Exercise 00 : ft_strcpy
Reproduce the behavior of the function strcpy (man strcpy).
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 01 : ft_strncpy
Reproduce the behavior of the function strncpy (man strncpy).
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 02 : ft_str_is_alpha
Create a function that returns 1 if the string given as a parameter contains only alphabetical characters, 
and 0 if it contains any other character. It should return 1 if str is empty
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 03 : ft_str_is_numeric
Create a function that returns 1 if the string given as a parameter contains only
digits, and 0 if it contains any other character. It should return 1 if str is empty.
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 04 : ft_str_is_lowercase
Create a function that returns 1 if the string given as a parameter contains only
lowercase alphabetical characters, and 0 if it contains any other character. It should return 1 if str is empty.
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 05 : ft_str_is_uppercase
Create a function that returns 1 if the string given as a parameter contains only
uppercase alphabetical characters, and 0 if it contains any other character. It should return 1 if str is empty.
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 06 : ft_str_is_printable
Create a function that returns 1 if the string given as a parameter contains only printable characters, 
and 0 if it contains any other character. It should return 1 if str is empty.
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 07 : ft_strupcase
Create a function that transforms every letter to uppercase. It should return str.
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 08 : ft_strlowcase
Create a function that transforms every letter to lowercase. It should return str.
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 09 : ft_strcapitalize
Create a function that capitalizes the first letter of each word and transforms all other letters to lowercase. 
A word is a string of alphanumeric characters. It should return str.
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 10 : ft_strlcpy
Reproduce the behavior of the function strlcpy (man strlcpy).
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 11 : ft_putstr_non_printable
Create a function that displays a string of characters onscreen. If this string contains characters 
that aren’t printable, they’ll have to be displayed in the shape ofhexadecimals (lowercase), 
preceeded by a "backslash".
Allowed functions: write

Exercise 12 : ft_print_memory
Create a function that displays the memory area onscreen. The display of this memory area should 
be split into three "columns" separated by
a space :
◦ The hexadecimal address of the first line’s first character followed by a ’:’.
◦ The content in hexadecimal with a space each 2 characters and should be
padded with spaces if needed.
◦ The content in printable characters.
If a character is non-printable, it’ll be replaced by a dot. Each line should handle sixteen characters.
If size equals to 0, nothing should be displayed.
Allowed functions: write
