Exercise 00 : ft_strlen
Create a function that counts and returns the number of characters in a string.
Allowed functions: None

Exercise 01 : ft_putstr
Create a function that displays a string of characters on the standard output.
Allowed functions: write

Exercise 02 : ft_putnbr
Create a function that displays the number entered as a parameter. The function
has to be able to display all possible values within an int type variable.
Allowed functions: write

Exercise 03 : ft_atoi
Write a function that converts the initial portion of the string pointed by str to its int
representation. The string can start with an arbitray amount of white space (as determined by isspace(3)).
The string can be followed by an arbitrary amount of + and - signs, - sign will change the sign of the int 
returned based on the number of - is odd or even. Finally the string can be followed by any numbers of the base 10.
Your function should read the string until the string stop following the rules and return the number found until now.
You should not take care of overflow or underflow. result can be undefined in that case.
Allowed functions: None
Here’s an example of a program that prints the atoi return value:
$>./a.out "  ---+--+1234ab567"
-1234

Exercise 04 : ft_putnbr_base
Create a function that displays a number in a base system in the terminal. This number is given in the shape of an int, 
and the radix in the shape of a string of characters.The base-system contains all useable symbols to display that number :
◦ 0123456789 is the commonly used base system to represent decimal numbers
◦ 01 is a binary base system ;
◦ 0123456789ABCDEF an hexadecimal base system ;
◦ poneyvif is an octal base system.
The function must handle negative numbers. If there’s an invalid argument, nothing should be displayed. 
Examples of invalid arguments :
◦ base is empty or size of 1;
◦ base contains the same character twice ;
◦ base contains + or - .
Allowed functions: write

Exercise 05 : ft_atoi_base
Write a function that converts the initial portion of the string pointed by str to int
representation.
• str is in a specific base given as a second parameter.
• excepted the base rule, the function should work exactly like ft_atoi.
If there’s an invalid argument, the function should return 0. Examples of invalid
arguments :
◦ base is empty or size of 1;
◦ base contains the same character twice ;
◦ base contains + or - or whitespaces.
Allowed functions: None

